(this["webpackJsonpquiz-app-starter"]=this["webpackJsonpquiz-app-starter"]||[]).push([[0],{10:function(e,t,r){"use strict";r.r(t);var s=r(0),n=r.n(s),a=r(3),o=r.n(a),i=(r(9),r(1));function c(){var e=[{questionText:"ASAP Rocky's mother named him after...?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Rocky Balboa",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Rocky Marciano",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:'Rakim from "Eric.B. & Rakim"',isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Randomly",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"What city is ASAP Rocky from?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Manhattan",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Harlem",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Queens",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Brooklyn",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"What tattoo does ASAP Rocky have across his stomach?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"A$AP LIFE",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"A$AP WORLD",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"LIVE A$AP",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"LOVE A$AP",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"What does ASAP stand for?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"As Soon As Possible",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Anything Stands As Peace",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Always Sing About Peace",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Always Strive and Prosper",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"What is ASAP Rocky's zodiac sign?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Scorpio",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Libra",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Gemini",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Taurus",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Aside from being in ASAP, Rocky is also part of...?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"AWGE",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"YG",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Cactus Jack Records",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Secret Sound Club",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"ASAP Rocky said if he wasn't a rapper, he would be...?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Singer",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Photographer",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Engineer",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Interior Designer",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"What is ASAP Rocky's producer name?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Lord Flacko",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Lord Flvcko",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"RockyTheProducer",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"ASAP R",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"ASAP Rocky is featured in which game's soundtrack?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Assassin's Creed: Valhalla",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Cyberpunk 2077",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Call of Duty: Cold War",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Fortnite",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"In Rocky's music video 'Fashion Killa' he co-stars with...?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Kendall Jenner",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Chanel Iman",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Iggy Azalea",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Rihanna",isCorrect:!0}]}],t=(document.getElementsByClassName("app"),Object(s.useState)(0)),r=Object(i.a)(t,2),a=r[0],o=r[1],c=Object(s.useState)(!1),u=Object(i.a)(c,2),w=u[0],l=u[1],x=Object(s.useState)(0),T=Object(i.a)(x,2),C=T[0],m=T[1];return n.a.createElement("div",{className:"app"},w?n.a.createElement("div",{className:"score-section"},"You scored ",C," out of ",e.length,n.a.createElement("button",{id:"reset-quiz",onClick:function(){return m(0),o(0),void l(!1)}},"Reset Quiz")):n.a.createElement(n.a.Fragment,null,n.a.createElement("div",{className:"question-section"},n.a.createElement("div",{className:"question-count"},n.a.createElement("span",null,"Question ",a+1),"/",e.length),n.a.createElement("div",{className:"question-text"},e[a].questionText)),n.a.createElement("div",{className:"answer-section"},e[a].answerOptions.map((function(t){return n.a.createElement("button",{onClick:function(){return function(t){!0===t&&m(C+1);var r=a+1;r<e.length?o(r):l(!0)}(t.isCorrect)}},t.answerText)})))))}o.a.render(n.a.createElement(n.a.StrictMode,null,n.a.createElement(c,null)),document.getElementById("root"))},4:function(e,t,r){e.exports=r(10)},9:function(e,t,r){}},[[4,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.f9f9ca46.chunk.js.map